http://christianseniorservices.org/privacy-policy

Skip to main content
Search form
Search
Main menu
About UsCOVID-19 OperationsCEO UpdatesBoard of TrusteesLeadershipFinancialsContact UsOur ServicesMeals on WheelsMeal DeliverySign up for mealsMenuEmergency MealsNutrition EducationSenior Center MealsGrace PlaceAniMealsFriendly Visitorcomfy casasGrace NotesGet MealsMeal ReferralMenuVolunteerVolunteer PortalWays to VolunteerFriendly VisitorVolunteer of the MonthDonateGive NowPlanned GivingCorporate GivingHoliday DonationNews & MoreIn the NewsBlogEventsSignup For Our E-NewsletterHelp and Resources
Main menu
About UsCOVID-19 OperationsCEO UpdatesBoard of TrusteesLeadershipFinancialsContact UsOur ServicesMeals on WheelsMeal DeliverySign up for mealsMenuEmergency MealsNutrition EducationSenior Center MealsGrace PlaceAniMealsFriendly Visitorcomfy casasGrace NotesGet MealsMeal ReferralMenuVolunteerVolunteer PortalWays to VolunteerFriendly VisitorVolunteer of the MonthDonateGive NowPlanned GivingCorporate GivingHoliday DonationNews & MoreIn the NewsBlogEventsSignup For Our E-NewsletterHelp and Resources
You are hereHome Privacy Policy
OUR PRIVACY POLICY
Meals on Wheels San Antonio respects the privacy of those who use our website, and the following policy is intended to help you understand how we use the information we collect.
HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION
Our website automatically collects non-personally identifiable information on our site visitors. This information is used to compile statistics for our website, such as the number of visitors to the site and which pages were viewed.
Personally identifiable information is only collected when you voluntarily submit it, such as through making a donation on our website. If you provide us with this information we may use it to contact you about Meals on Wheels San Antonio. If you would prefer not to receive such correspondence, please let us know by sending us an email.
We may also occasionally share your mailing address information with vendors for the purposes of sending you information about Meals on Wheels San Antonio. We will not give out your email address. If you would rather we do not share any of your information, please send us an email. Be sure to provide your full name and mailing address so we can accurately update your information.
We do not share or sell donor information gathered offline or online.
DATA SECURITY
If you submit your personal information through our website, it is protected using industry-standard SSL encryption and https security protocol. Once your information has been transmitted to us, we have put in place appropriate procedures to keep it secure, and it will only be accessible to authorized personnel.
Meals on Wheels America
Current menu
Because of the COVID-19 pandemic there are no monthly menus at this time.
Clients will receive meal deliveries twice a week based on where they live.
We will not be delivering hot meals, beverages or fresh fruit at this time.
We will deliver additional food such as breakfast packs when possible.
View Full Menu
WHY MEALS ON WHEELS ?
4306 NW Loop 410
San Antonio, TX 78229
Tax ID: 74-1948646
Tel:
210.735.5115
Fax:
210.735.5659
Tollfree:
866.80.MOWSA (866.806.6972)
Search form
Search
Phone: 210.735.5115<>/p>
Fax: 210.735.5659
© 2020 Meals on Wheels San Antonio. All Rights Reserved.Website by: OneEach Technologies
